Batman: Strange Days is a action, animation film directed by Bruce Timm.
A lost tale from Batman's past, the Dark Knight tracks a strange
giant to the mysterious lair of Hugo Strange.
Batman (voice), played by Kevin Conroy.
Hugo Strange (voice), played by Brian George.
Woman (voice), played by Tara Strong.
Monster Man (voice), played by Bruce Timm.
Batman: Strange Days is a 2014 animated superhero short film
based on the popular DC Comics character Batman.
Directed by Bruce Timm, it was created to celebrate the 75th
anniversary of the conception of the character.
The film explores themes of superhero, based on comic,
period drama, nostalgic, aggressive.
The tone is dark.